{
    "subject": "resource/Centerville,_Indiana",
    "predicate": "ontology/isPartOf",
    "object": "resource/Indiana",
    "human_readable": "Centerville, Indiana is part of Indiana.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.986426591873169,
            "question": "What state is Centerville, Indiana part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.954419732093811,
            "question": "What are some notable features of Centerville, Indiana?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6997703313827515,
            "question": "Where is Centerville located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.693720281124115,
            "question": "Can you name a city that is part of Indiana?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.544033944606781,
            "question": "Is Centerville a city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5092530250549316,
            "question": "What is the geographic location of Centerville?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4195003807544708,
            "question": "Does Centerville have a specific county it belongs to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4181135892868042,
            "question": "To which US state does Centerville belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3365423083305359,
            "question": "Are there any historical landmarks in Centerville?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2060922235250473,
            "question": "Is Centerville in the Midwest region of the US?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Centerville, Indiana is part of Indiana.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4432_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any historical landmarks in Centerville?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4432_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which US state does Centerville belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4432_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Centerville have a specific county it belongs to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4432_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4432_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4432_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4432_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4432_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4432_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4432_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4432_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4432_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4432_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4432_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Centerville is located within the state of Indiana, specifically mentioning it as being situated just west of Richmond, Indiana. This supports the statement that Centerville is part of Indiana."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}